How do you feel about exams?
你怎么看待考试这件事？
Is it the one thing you dread or an experience you relish because it's your time to shine?
它是你最害怕的事情，还是你乐于享受的经历——因为这是你大放异彩的时刻？
Every year, many young people sit exams and whether they love or loathe them, most of them will face some anxiety in the lead up to the big day.
每年都有许多年轻人参加考试，无论他们喜欢还是讨厌考试，他们中的大多数人在考试来临前都会感到些许焦虑。
If you're anxious about your exams, don't worry, you're not alone.
如果你对考试感到焦虑，别担心，不止你一个人这样。
It might seem like a stressful time when the pressure is on to pass that all-important test but take a deep breath and absorb some good advice from people who've been through the same experience as you.
要通过那场至关重要的考试，压力确实很大，这段时间可能会让人倍感紧张，但深呼吸，听听那些和你有过同样经历的人的实用建议吧。
Eating the right food can feed your brain and keep you alert.
吃合适的食物能为大脑补充能量，让你保持清醒。
Nutritional therapist Kerry Torrens recommends making breakfast the most important meal of the day.
营养治疗师凯瑞·托伦斯建议让早餐为一天中最重要的一餐。
She recommends eating energy-giving oats and eggs, which contain a nutrient called choline - thought to help cognitive performance and improve memory as we age.
她推荐食用能提供能量的燕麦和鸡蛋，它们含有一种名为胆碱的营养素——这种物质被认为有助于提升认知能力，还能随着年龄增长改善记忆力。
And don't forget to drink lots of water to keep you hydrated – some research even suggests students who take water into the exam hall may even improve their grades.
另外别忘了多喝水，保持身体水分充足——有研究甚至表明，带水进考场的学生，成绩可能会更好。
One thing I know I always need is a good night's sleep to help me work and think better the next day and that's what's recommended for anyone preparing for their exams.
我一直都知道，睡个好觉可以让我第二天更好地工作和思考，这也是给所有备考者的建议。
If you get good sleep your memory is better and that means you can retain the information you have revised.
如果你休息的好，你的记忆力会更好，这意味着你能记住复习过的内容。
And it's good to wind down before bedtime too – no watching TV or chatting on social media!
睡前放松也很重要——别再看电视或再社交媒体上聊天了！
A good way to reduce your stress is to write down your anxieties.
有一个减轻压力的好方法，那就是把你的焦虑写下来。
This is something that Lisa Artis from the Sleep Council recommends because it can 'free your mind'.
这是睡眠委员会的莉萨·阿蒂斯推荐的方法，因为它能“解放你的大脑”。
She also says sitting on your bed when you're cramming is not a good idea because then you associate that place with stress.
她还说，临阵磨枪时坐在床上不是个好主意，因为这样会让你把床这个地方和压力联系起来。
Revising for exams can also sometimes seem relentless, so it's good to take breaks and reward yourself with a small treat, like a cake or a quick run around the block.
备考复习有时也会让人觉得没完没了，所以适当休息、给自己一点小奖励是很有必要的，比如一块蛋糕，或者绕着街区快速跑一圈。
There comes a point when your brain can't absorb any more information so you'll also need to know when to stop.
当你的大脑再也吸收不了更多信息时，你也需要知道该何时停下。
But if all this talk about revising and exams is still stressing you out, be assured that there are some people who will always be more on edge than you: your parents!
但如果这些关于复习和考试的讨论，还是让你感到压力山大，那请放心，总有一些人会比你更紧张：那就是你的父母！
They're there to support you but they'll be biting their fingernails, worrying about you and the final results.
他们会在你身边支持你，但也会紧张得坐立不安，为你和最终的成绩担心。
So maybe you need to give them some advice - chill, everything will be ok!
所以或许你该给他们提提建议——放轻松，一切都会好的！